<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on Home | Atticlab</title>
    <link>/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on Home | Atticlab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>

	<atom:link href="/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

  <item>
    <title>ICO is dead, long live TTO.</title>
    <link>/news/ico-dead/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

    <guid>/news/ico-dead/</guid>
    <description>At Attic Lab we think that retail investor participation in funding start-ups is of paramount importance for the blockchain sector to realise its full disruptive potential.</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>How to Use Our Dsp-Package</title>
    <link>/news/how-to-use-dsp/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

    <guid>/news/ico-dead/</guid>
    <description>At Attic Lab we think that retail investor participation in funding start-ups is of paramount importance for the blockchain sector to realise its full disruptive potential.</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Mobile version of MyEOSWallet</title>
    <link>/news/mob-version-eos-wallet/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 6 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

    <guid>/news/ico-dead/</guid>
    <description>At Attic Lab we think that retail investor participation in funding start-ups is of paramount importance for the blockchain sector to realise its full disruptive potential.</description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Chintai Proxy Adds Attic Lab</title>
    <link>/news/chintai/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

    <guid>/news/ico-dead/</guid>
    <description>At Attic Lab we think that retail investor participation in funding start-ups is of paramount importance for the blockchain sector to realise its full disruptive potential.</description>
  </item>

    <item>
      <title>5 reasons why you want to vote for Attic Lab</title>
      <link>/news/five-reasons/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>/news/five-reasons/</guid>
      <description>Financial technology avant-garde Attic Lab is a fintech and blockchain solutions company. During these years, a lot of experience was accumulated. There were numbers of successful projects with Ukrainian National Bank, private banks, blockchain-based banking platform, cryptocurrency exchange, national cryptocurrency project and a bank concept focused on new know-hows like Big Data, IoT and blockchain-based technologies.
Going through these projects, Attic Lab had worked with different aspects and angles which led to combination of all the knowledge about development, DevOps, finance, legal systems and the main thing – a dialog with user.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>EOS.IO Consensus Algorithm</title>
      <link>/news/eos-io-algorithm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>/news/eos-io-algorithm/</guid>
      <description>Since a few questions about EOS are still in the air, Attic Lab created this post to ensure that everything is straightforward and clear in terms of understanding EOS consensus algorithm. Here, we are covering everything from the beginning: what is DPoS and its difference comparing to PoS. selection of block producers, and how the consensus is achieved among block producers. Enjoy!
EOS.IO uses the DPoS (Delegated Proof-of-Stake) consensus algorithm that allows you to create blocks within 0.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>How to Install EOS Node on LINUX. Step-by-step guide by Attic Lab.</title>
      <link>/news/eos-node-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>/news/eos-node-linux/</guid>
      <description>Attic Lab is very excited to present you this guide about how to install EOS node on Linux. In this post, we will cover all steps that you should follow to successfully run EOSIO on your system. Let’s begin.
EOSIO consists of set of programs and the main of them are:
 nodeos - the core EOSIO node daemon that can be configured with plugins to run a node. Example uses are block production, dedicated API endpoints, and local development.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Attic Lab Becomes an Official EOS Block Producer Candidate</title>
      <link>/news/eos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>/news/eos/</guid>
      <description>We are excited to announce that Attic Lab is an official EOS Block Producer candidate.
Exactly as it sounds, block producers will produce the blocks of the EOS blockchain. EOS block producers are located worldwide and come from different technical, social and organizational backgrounds.
EOS block producer is a decentralized body that is voted in to govern the EOS network for a particular amount of time. This means that EOS block producers will be changing on a regular basis.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Announcing The Launch Of Our Newly Redesigned Website</title>
      <link>/news/new-atticlab-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>/news/new-atticlab-design/</guid>
      <description>We’re excited to announce the launch of our redesigned website. The Attic Lab’s website www.atticlab.net has been completely redesigned and upgraded.
Our goal was to provide our visitors with a simple way to discover more about our expertise, our projects and solutions we realize for our clients from all over the world.
First of all, it’s fully adaptive, meaning that the website is now compatible with any device, like desktops, laptops, netbooks, tablets etc.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Attic Lab Takes Part in ISO Blockchain Standardization Process</title>
      <link>/news/iso/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>/news/iso/</guid>
      <description>Blockchain technology has a great potential to revolutionize transactions and, therefore, increase efficiency throughout the financial sector.
So in autumn 2017, Attic Lab together with Deloitte, REMME, and BFU formed the Ukrainian ISO Committee to kick off the Blockchain Standardization process.
Being a legal as well as Blockchain expert, Deloitte initialized the project, while Attic Lab contributed as an expert in development and innovation technology.
We are extremely proud to be a part of such an important ongoing initiative and work alongside with outstanding professionals to set the future course of Blockchain standardization in the financial and banking sectors.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Attic Lab officially announces its EOS Block Producer Candidacy.</title>
      <link>/news/attic-announces-eos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>/news/attic-announces-eos/</guid>
      <description>Attic Lab was founded in 2016. In the very beginning we developed blockchain solutions for banks and other financial institutions in collaboration with Ambisafe, Alliance Bank and Humaniq. Now our diverse and experienced team allows us to focus on building own blockchain applications. Our recent projects include cryptocurrency exchange Cryptagio and open-source banking software openbankIT.
Mission of Attic Lab is to create a compliant and decentralized financial system that benefits all its participants.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Attic Lab has successfully launched a new project - Cryptagio.com</title>
      <link>/news/cryptagio-launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>/news/cryptagio-launch/</guid>
      <description>We are proud to announce the successful launch of our recent project - Cryptagio digital asset exchange.
Our team has a proven track record in investment, banking and trading sectors as well as extensive skill set in design, engineering and marketing. We joined our forces, consolidated insights and co-create token-based solutions that ensure consistent development and stability of the platform.
Cryptagio was built to accommodate those, striving to get ahead and take hold in today’s crypto market, regardless of their level of experience.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>EOS blockchain launch. How to claim your EOS tokens</title>
      <link>/news/register-eos-tokens/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>/news/register-eos-tokens/</guid>
      <description>June 1st is a small celebration – EOS Mainnet launch. Many of us decided to participate in EOS tokens distribution and now, we need to register them. How it works?
During the ICO period, EOS tokens used Ethereum blockchain, however, starting on June 1st 2018, EOS will run its own blockchain and all the tokens that are not registered will be frozen and non-transferable. So, be sure to register the address where you keep your tokens prior to the June 1st 2018.</description>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
